Lord Tokito!
Don't underestimate me, you damn brat.
I won't let you play spell kidding!
闇を駆け抜けて
何処向かう?
月明かりだ何処どれだれ eigentlichが
只七つの道のskirt
痛みも悲しみも
иль
ire
I'll see you next time.
How dare you speak to me so disrespectfully, you miserable brat!
As if someone who's only lived a decade could ever hope to behead me!
I might be young, but I despise everything about you, so I'm sure I'll find a way.
From the way you look and talk, everything about you is creepy.
You simply can't appreciate my beauty, my grace, or my elegance because an imbecile like you is too uneducated and poor to comprehend it.
The same way a dung beetle couldn't read a book if its life depended on it!
Now that you mention it, you do sort of look like a dung beetle.
You're the dung beetle, dammit! Look at you with your short limbs and that small, pathetic blade! You couldn't reach my neck even if you tried!
Strange. If I'm not mistaken, I did earlier. And unless I'm blind, your limbs are shorter than mine.
Oh, I get it now. You were just thinking out loud about yourself. I'm sorry I interrupted.
Yahoo! My, what a childish insult! Don't tell me you really thought that would be enough to fluster me!
I can see now how desperate you are to win! What a sad sight to look upon!
Hmm. Hmm.
Ha ha! What's wrong?
It's really bugging me. That odd vase of yours. Why is it misshapen?
Hmm. It's not symmetrical, is it?
What a sad sight to look upon.
How dare you critique my art with those rotten eyeballs of yours!
My face is perfect!
And certainly not misshapen!
Blood demon art!
Ten thousand gliding slime fish!
Once my ten thousand assassins are finished picking you clean to the bone!
I'll make you into one of my beloved works!
Mist breathing.
Sixth form. Lunar dispersing mist.
What? He slashed them all at once?
His speed and attack range have increased!
Why isn't my poison having an effect on him?
I didn't expect this!
Regardless, I have nothing to worry about!
You've dealt with the immediate threat, but before those fish turn to dust, they'll disperse more poison!
And since it's transdermal poison they release, it can also be absorbed through the skin!
Get hit with that, and you're finished!
Mist breathing.
Third form.
Scattering mist splash!
What?
He blasted them all away with just that one swing!
You can shed your skin.
You're proving to be a real pain in the butt.
Stop wasting my time hiding in trees and just fight me.
Prepare yourself or you're about to witness my true form!
Go on.
Only two people before you have seen me in this state!
Really, that many?
Shut up!
No one's left to tell the tale once I've started taking things seriously!
How amazing.
Shut your mouth, you dim-witted brat!
I'll have you know my translucent scales are harder and stronger than diamonds!
I needed each one inside my face!
Behold my artistry in its perfect, beautiful form!
Bow down before me in awe!
Heh heh heh heh...
Huh?
Say something, you worthless puppet!
Quit playing dumb with me!
You really know how to rep someone the wrong way, don't you, brat?
But...
You just told me to shut my mouth earlier.
Besides...
It didn't really warrant a reaction.
You just told me not to go hiding in trees.
You're proving to be a pain in the butt.
No, the only reason I'm up here is to hide from your stench.
So, what do you think of my god-like power, hmm?
Everything my fish touch, turn into the most amazing fish you've seen!
Not to mention my speed, along with the unparalleled flexibility I have with this springy body!
On top of that, my rippling scales allow me to move without restraint!
I'm unstoppable!
I can see you're so terrified, you're trembling!
But believe it or not, I still haven't gotten serious!
So, what do you think of my god-like power, hmm?
Everything my fish touch, turn into the most amazing fish you've seen!
Not to mention my speed, along with the unparalleled flexibility I have with this springy body!
On top of that, my rippling scales allow me to move without restraint!
I'm unstoppable!
I can see you're so terrified, you're trembling!
But believe it or not, I still haven't gotten serious!
Even the most jaw-dropping attack is pointless if you can't land it!
Remember, that boiling fury within me!
As I watched maggots infest my beloved brother's body as he began to rot,
I found myself on the brink of death, and the maggots started feeding on me.
Boil some water right away, and start applying clean cloths to their wounds!
Yes, Mother!
How's the older brother?
He passed away before we came!
Do everything in your power to keep the younger brother alive!
Yes, Mother!
Brother...
I was fortunate enough to be rescued.
Had I not, I would have died.
Lord Tokito!
You're not fully healed yet, you shouldn't...
I may have lost my memory, but my body remembers.
That fury will rage within me until I die.
It's how I pushed myself past my limits, how I trained until I vomited blood, to annihilate the demons, to put an end to their kind once and for all.
Bear witness to my unbridled strength in all its glory!
Blood demon art, killer fish skin!
How I pushed myself past my limits.
How I trained until I vomited blood.
To annihilate the demons.
To put an end to their kind once and for all.
Bear witness to my unbridled strength in all its glory!
Blood demon art!
Killer fish scales!
Now what do you think?
I doubt you've ever seen a demon move quite like this!
My scales allow me to move at will!
I'm impossible to predict!
My speed goes against the laws of nature, wouldn't you say?
I wonder what kind of art I should make out of your body.
Maybe I should rip off that ugly head of yours
and replace it with one of my lovely fish!
It's over for you!
Mist breathing.
Seventh form.
Obscuring clouds.
No!
There he is!
I found him!
Not there!
Over there, eh?
Woohoo!
Too slow!
What's this?
How can you vanish?
What's going on here?
Where did that brat go?
It's like, it's like, the area's being completely shrouded in mist.
So tell me, what made you think that you were the only one not taking this fight seriously?
What the hell?
Am I upside down?
What's going on here?
Why can't I sense anything?
That pest is finally showing himself!
I need to make sword work of him and report to Lord Muzan!
Am I running the door also?
Next can it next.
I don't have to remove Haha.
No.
Beheaded! Ridiculous! Impossible! Unbelievable! What an unheard of, abnormal situation did I actually lose?
Me? Lose? I lost to a child? Me of all people!
It's over for you. Farewell. Do everyone a favor and never be reborn again.
Curses! How could this have happened to me? A lowly human like you shouldn't be able to decapitate me!
You abominable, low-level life-form! My life is worth over a hundred of your wretched kind!
I am one of the chosen, exalted life-forms! You're nothing but weak flesh that grows old!
But I took your insignificant lives in my hands! And used those hands to elevate you all to worthy works of art!
You ignorant, vulgar little maggot!
I've heard more than enough. Now go to hell where you rightfully belong.
Come on!
Try not to be rigid about how you perceive the world around you, Murichiro.
Once you've rediscovered your unshakable self, you will become even more powerful.
It's exactly like the Master said to me.
As long as I have my unshakable self, I can dig in with both feet in all my might.
As long as I know who I am in my heart, all doubt and hesitation will disappear like the mist.
As long as I draw breath, no demon on earth can escape my blade.
Lord Tokito! Lord Tokito! Lord Tokito! You saved our lives! But are you all right?
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
Are you sure about that?
Yeah. Why wouldn't I feel incredible right now? I should get going. I have to join up with Tanjiro and the others.
I don't know. You're looking really pale, Lord Tokito. Are you certain you're all right?
Like I said, I'm totally fine. What makes you think otherwise?
Huh? I can hear you heaving! And I can see your whole body's trembling!
I'm okay. But if you don't mind, could you go ahead and check on Kotetsu and...
You're literally frothing at the mouth!
Ah! Lord Tokito! Oh crap! Oh crap! Is he about to die? What am I supposed to do?
Hey! Somebody!
Mr. Haganeska!
He's not coming to help, is he? I shouldn't be surprised. He ignored me when I was about to be murdered!
Mr. Haganeska! He's choking on the foam! This is bad! What? What? What should I do?
You should probably lay him on his side.
Huh? R-R-Right!
Huh?
Ah! It's the ghost of Yanko Tetsu!
Don't worry! I'm not a ghost! I'd have to be dead for that!
No! They all say that! Ghosts are never aware they're ghosts or that they're even dead!
Yeah, I know, but I'm alive!
No, no, no, no! Your solar plexus! How could you possibly be alive after losing all that blood?
Oh, this? This is the blood from the arm they slashed. It must have smeared on my chest.
My arm wound's pretty deep, though, and if it doesn't stop bleeding, then I might actually be dead soon.
Oh yeah, as for my belly...
That's where I was carrying the guard Mr. Tanjiro gave me. It saved me.
He specifically said he wanted it to be the guard on his new sword.
Let's give it our all as Hashira!
See? Everything turned out just fine.
Father...
Mother...
Muichiro...
You did great.
Brother...
Thank you.
There are five wooden dragon heads. They can expand to about 66 feet.
All right, I've got one thing figured out.
Shilukami Kagura. Clear blue.
My eardrums just burst. I'm so dizzy. I can't get up. It's no good. Get on your feet. Hurry! Here comes an attack!
Here comes an attack!
It can use the powers of the Four Emotions!
Not only that, but the power's been magnified!
No time to use breathing skills, and I can't heal!
I can't handle the attacks anymore, even if I anticipate them!
I can't catch my breath. But if I can somehow get 66 feet away...
All right, I can do this!
It's stretching!
Use a technique! Slash it!
Slash it!
It's hopeless. I'm getting crushed!
It's over.
Such a ghastly monster! What is that thing?
Ms. Konrochi?
You okay? I'm sorry I'm so late. That was a close one.
Ms. Konrochi!
Tanjiro!
Take a well-deserved break! Great job out there! I'm proud!
I-I can't hear because my eardrums burst!
Tanjiro...
I promise I'll rescue Nezuko and Genya, alright?
Annoying girl...
So just leave the rest of me!
Whoa, wait! Upper rank! It's upper four!
...
or
Thank you.
I can't detect any traces of the enemy.
Where the heck is the enemy?
Nowhere, because our turn isn't happening for a while.
Oh boy.
We're going to carry out this mission and move on to the next one.
Next, episode 10, Love Hashira meets Shuri Kanroji.
You better demolish that upper race demon.
You got that?
They're Pachiro!